jackpotcity.co.uk 2011-02-08

# JackpotCity.com Online Casino – Security and Privacy

This site is operated by Tower Rock Ltd (our "Site"). We have created this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to outline our firm commitment to your privacy. Our policy is based on the Gibraltar Data Protection Act 2004 and the principles held within that Act. It will also inform you of type of Personal Data we process when you use our Site, why we process this Data and how we use this Data.

By using www.jackpotcity.com you acknowledge and accept both the rules, terms and conditions of this privacy policy and the purposes and methods of processing for which your Personal Data is collected.

How your Personal Data is stored and used 

During the registration process and when you subsequently use your JackpotCity.com account, specific Personal Data ("Personal Data") is collected including, but not limited to, first and last name, date of birth, credit card Data, home or other physical address, email address, phone number or other contact Data.

Your Personal Data is held by us on servers based in Gibraltar and Canada and elsewhere from time to time.

All of your Data is collected and stored in a secure and protected environment and is correct as it is provided. You are entitled by law to have a copy of the Personal Data recorded and to have any Personal Data corrected. You may change your personal details at anytime by sending us an email <

>or by writing to us at Customer Service, Tower Rock Ltd, Suite 651 Europort, Gibraltar.

Disclosure of your Personal Data will only take place in accordance with applicable laws. Such disclosure will primarily be to other Tower Rock companies, business partners, service providers, consultants or suppliers that are engaged to carry out financial or other processing on our behalf.

Due to the nature of the internet, its use to collect and transfer Personal Data it may necessitate the transmission of your Personal Data outside of the EEA. By using this site you acknowledge and agree to our use of your Personal Data in this manner. We do not collect your Personal Data when you use our Site without your knowledge or rent, sell or trade your Personal Data to any third party.

You may ‘opt out’ of receiving any promotional communications either by choosing to opt out where such option is made available on the Site or in an email you receive from us, or at any time by sending an email <

>or by writing to us at Customer Service, Tower Rock Ltd, Suite 651 Europort, Gibraltar.

Security of Processing

Your security as a customer is of the utmost importance to us. Online security measures such as passwords and account numbers are used when all transactions take place to ensure that no one can gain access to your financial or personal details.` When you open an account at JackpotCity.com Online Casino, your details are fully encrypted by the strictest 128-bit SSL encryption for total security. When Personal Data is transferred over the Internet, we and our e-commerce partner use 128-Bit Secure Socket Layer Encryption Technology to ensure the security of all Personal Data.

All commercial transactions at JackpotCity.com Online Casino are facilitated by Datacash Ltd, the internet’s premier e-cash merchant. They provide our Customers with safe and secure e-cash and play an active role in fraud prevention and detection. Their aim is to ensure the integrity of client’s accounts and safeguard payments made to you. Risk sentinel, advanced fraud-management software that protects JackpotCity.com Online Casino customers from online fraud, has been implemented to provide you with ongoing protection.

Fraud Prevention

To protect us and any other users of the Site against fraud including use of stolen credit cards, or any other fraudulent or criminal activity (including any chargeback or other reversal of a payment) we may check your details against, and share Personal Data with other online gaming sites, banks, credit card companies and other fraud prevention agencies. In addition, money laundering legislation requires all financial institutions to collect and record Personal Data to confirm a customer’s identity and to report any transactions arousing suspicion.

Cookies

Cookies are small files of Data which are stored on your computer. On your first visit to <http://www.jackpotcity.com/>, a piece of Personal Data called a cookie will be sent to your browser for the purpose of tracking your navigation patterns. You can disable cookies by changing your browser settings. However, please note that the functionality of our website will be impaired.

Legal Disclaimer

Please also visit our rules, terms and conditions covering the use and limitations of liability governing the use of the JackpotCity.com Online Casino web site and software.

Other linked websites

Where there is a link from this website to another relevant site, this privacy policy will not apply once you leave this site.

Your consent

By clicking "I agree" during the registration process or by your continued use of the Site following the posting of this Privacy Policy (as applicable), you agree to this Privacy Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with our [Rules, Terms and Conditions](http://www.jackpotcity.com/rules.aspx "JackpotCity.com Online Casino Rules"). We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy and will notify you of these changes by posting the modified terms on our online site.
